https://www.comforthouse.com/privacypledge.html

Tweet
Home > The Comfort House Story > Privacy PledgePrivacy Policy StatementThis is the web site of Comfort House, the leading on-line shopping
site for products that make your life easier and more comfortable.Our order form asks you to supply us with information specific to your order.
The information that you provide is used to process and send your order.
We
also use the information to contact you if there is a problem with your order.
We may also contact you by email for feedback on our products and services and to
provide occasional new product or special sale announcements.
Comfort House does not sell or share your name, address, phone number, email
address, or any other personal information, with any other company.
If you do not wish to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending
an email to the address below.Our site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and
order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this
information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo!
also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please visit the Yahoo homepage and select the Privacy Policy link at the bottom of it for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.Retargeted Advertising: As you browse Comfort House, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer by a third party display advertising partner so that we can understand what you are interested in.
This enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Comfort House. The techniques our partner employs do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.
You can visit this page to opt out of targeted advertising. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, we can be reached
at customerservice@comforthouse.com or by telephone
at 1-800-359-7701 (973-242-8080 outside USA).
Our postal address is: Comfort House, 189 Frelinghuysen Ave., Newark, NJ 07114 USA.Thank you for shopping with Comfort House!TestimonialsRead more...
Custom Address SignsPersonalized GiftsLaser Engraving ServicesShippingReturn PolicyPrice Match PolicyVolume Pricing / Bulk DiscountsOrdering & Payment MethodsDelivery to APO AddressesDelivery to Canada & InternationallyProduct IndexPrivacy PolicyAbout Comfort HouseWhy Shop With Us?
Contact Us.Comfort House is a small independent retailer and manufacturer established in 1991. There are many imitators of our name and original ideas but there is only one Comfort House.Thank you for shopping with us and for supporting small business!Entire Site Contents © Copyright 1991-2020, Comfort House, All Rights Reserved.
